josephprinceonline.com 2019-05-21

# Privacy Policy | JosephPrince.com

At JosephPrince.com, your privacy is of utmost importance to us and we take every measure to ensure that the data provided by you is kept secure and not misused. We will not use your personal information for any purpose other than that which it was given for.

When dealing with your personal information, JosephPrince.com adheres to all obligations set forth in Singapore’s Personal Data Protection Act. This policy dictates how we use your personal information that we collect.

## Information You Choose To Submit

### When you sign up for a JosephPrince.com account

When you register for an account on JosephPrince.com, you will be required to provide us with your email address. The email address you provide will only be used to send you information about your orders, or to contact you about any important matters regarding your account. Please note that the password you will need to create to login will be securely stored and is accessible to no one but yourself.

Should you choose to opt-in to our email newsletters during your registration, your email address will be added to the respective mailing lists you have selected. You can opt-out from these mailing lists at any time. For more information on our privacy policy regarding emails, click here..

### Shopping on JosephPrince.com

When you place an online order, you will be required to provide the following information: your name, email address, delivery address, billing address, contact number and any special delivery instructions. We may share selected information with our agents, sub-contractors (e.g. shipping company) and/or third parties (e.g. PayPal, the payment gateway that you make payments through) for the sole purpose of fulfilling your order.

Please note that JosephPrince.com does not collect or receive your payment card details. This information is only received by PayPal, our payment gateway. For more details on PayPal’s privacy policy, click here.

### Emails from JosephPrince.com

JosephPrince.com has found that attractive, graphics-rich emails are a quick and effective way to communicate with our registered users and subscribers about new resources, and clearance and sale items. We maintain an opt-in, user-customizable subscription database of users who have requested to receive these emails. Every email you receive provides an option for you to unsubscribe from such emails if you so wish to.

### When You Fill Out a Form or Send Us an Email

If you choose to provide us with personal information by sending an email to JosephPrince.com, or by filling out a form with your personal information and submitting it through the web site, we may use the information to respond to your message and to help us provide you with the information that you have requested.

### When You Send Us a Testimony

Should you wish to send us your testimony to encourage readers of this website, be assured that before it is published, a separate release agreement will be sent to you for your consent.

### When you participate in any contest or promotion

When you participate in any contest or promotion, we may ask for your name, address, email address and/or other information so that we can administer the contest/promotion and notify winners. Unless you have given us permission to do so, we will not add you to our mailing lists or use your information for other purposes.

## Information We Collect Automatically

### Visiting JosephPrince.com

We collect information automatically about your visit whenever you interact with this website, for example, when you browse through the website, read pages, or download information. This is done with the use of "cookies," which are small text files placed on your computer to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behaviour information in an anonymous form. Please be assured that this information is anonymised and cannot be used to identify you personally.

This information includes your Internet Protocol (IP) address, which is captured in our web server log files by default. This information will only be used internally to help diagnose problems with our server, and to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload, change information, or cause damage to our servers.

The information we collect from you will be used only for administrative purposes. Unless specifically mentioned to you at the point where the information is collected, or in this privacy policy, we will not release or sell your personal information to any third party without your permission except where JosephPrince.com considers the release appropriate to comply with the law, or to protect the rights, property and safety of JosephPrince.com, its members, or others.

In cases where we have obtained your permission to disclose your personal information to any third party, all such parties will be obliged to maintain the same or better level of security and confidentiality of your information as stated by this policy, and to process the data only according to our instruction.

## Accessing, Updating and Withdrawing Your Information

In accordance to the applicable laws of the Singapore government, JosephPrince.com will provide you with access to update or amend the personal information stored with us. In the event that you may wish to request access to, update, amend, or withdraw your personal information, you may contact our Data Protection Officer using the details in the Contact Us section of this policy.

Please note that for security reasons, JosephPrince.com, in accordance with this section, will take steps to authenticate the identity of the requesting party before providing access to the personal information requested.

## Retention of Your Information

Because JosephPrince.com website stores your personal information, we take reasonable steps to ensure the security of the personal and sensitive information we hold and to protect it against loss, misuse or unauthorized access, destruction, use, modification, or disclosure.

Our IT systems are password protected and comply with applicable security standards. Only authorised personnel are permitted to access these details.

It is our policy to:

  * Permanently de-identify personal information where reasonable and possible; and
  * Destroy personal information once the purpose which it was collected is no longer served.

## Variation

JosephPrince.com may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. We encourage you to visit the website regularly to stay updated with these changes.

## Governing Law

These Terms and Conditions shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of the Republic of Singapore. You hereby submit to the non-exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of the Republic of Singapore.

## Contact Us

The JosephPrince.com Data Protection Officer helps ensure compliance with this Privacy Policy and answers questions about data privacy or security issues. This Officer also helps educate JosephPrince.com employees concerning compliance to the policy. If you have questions, comments or concerns about data privacy, JosephPrince.com’s Privacy Policy or the security of personal information that we process, you may send an e-mail to [dpo@josephprince.com](mailto:dpo@josephprince.com)
